[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gojira is the result of combining two Japanese words.  What do these two words mean in English?", "correct_answer": "Whale and Ape", "incorrect_answers": ["Swim and Stomp", "King and Monster", "Lizard and Demon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After retiring from the US Presidency in 1797, this person became one of the most successful American distillers of whiskey.", "correct_answer": "George Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["James Maddison", "John Adams", "Andrew Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Boron?", "correct_answer": "B", "incorrect_answers": ["Bo", "Bn", "Br"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Choking Doberman from the popular urban legend choking on?", "correct_answer": "Human fingers", "incorrect_answers": ["A human ear", "A hairball", "A dolls head"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city in Colorado is known as the Richest Square Mile on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Central City, Colorado", "incorrect_answers": ["Denver, Colorado", "Leadville, Colorado", "Colorado Springs, Colorado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture for 1998 was given to this movie.", "correct_answer": "An Alan Smithee Film: Burn Hollywood Burn", "incorrect_answers": ["Spiceworld", "Godzilla", "Armageddon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turtle-doves tend to eat in their nests and high in the trees.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Red fescue is a type of what?", "correct_answer": "Grass", "incorrect_answers": ["Snake", "Tree", "Kangaroo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Io and Europa are two of the larger satellites of which Solar System planet?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Pluto", "Venus", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these not only cut off pieces of the American flag, but was honored for doing so?", "correct_answer": "Robert Peary", "incorrect_answers": ["Benedict Arnold", "Jefferson Davis", "John Paul Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the pirate freecreditreport.com ad, who stole the mans identity?", "correct_answer": "a hacker", "incorrect_answers": ["the Packers", "a Quaker", "a slacker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tall beauty plays Bren MacGuff in Juno but she may be more famous as C.J. Cregg on The West Wing.", "correct_answer": "Allison Janney", "incorrect_answers": ["Olivia Thirlby", "Ellen Page", "Jennifer Garner"]}]